<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Stellar.Casa - Beyond Stellar</title>
    <link>https://stellar.casa/blogs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Stellar.Casa - Beyond Stellar</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 23:32:50 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://stellar.casa/blogs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>submitXDR</title>
      <link>https://stellar.casa/blogs/submitxdr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 23:32:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stellar.casa/blogs/submitxdr/</guid>
      <description>Application to submit Signed XDR manually in simple Command Line interface
Features Lightweight application for submitting Signed Stellar Transactions. - Supports submitting any XDR - Supports Horizon Public and Test Network - Prints Response and Ledger Information for Success Transactions
Dependencies  Stellar Go SDK  Usage  Clone the repo
git clone github.com/aanupam23/submitXDR  Run this application using
go run submitXDR.go   Licence 
Stellar is trademark of Stellar Development Foundation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>teaStellar</title>
      <link>https://stellar.casa/blogs/teastellar/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 23:32:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stellar.casa/blogs/teastellar/</guid>
      <description>Coming Soon !!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>go-stellar-validate</title>
      <link>https://stellar.casa/blogs/go-stellar-validate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2019 12:32:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stellar.casa/blogs/go-stellar-validate/</guid>
      <description>Dependencies  Stellar Go SDK  Install go get -u github.com/aanupam23/go-stellar-validate  Getting Started  go-stellar-validate is a handy package for id validation in building Stellar applications. This package that helps in validating Stellar id&amp;rsquo;s such as Public Key, Private Key, Valid Asset Length, Transactions id before using them in your application.  :question: WIP - This Library is work in progress.
Contribute go-stellar-validate is open source and all contributions are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>go-stellar-IPFS</title>
      <link>https://stellar.casa/blogs/go-stellar-ipfs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 12:32:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stellar.casa/blogs/go-stellar-ipfs/</guid>
      <description>Dependencies  Stellar Go SDK go-ipfs-api  Install go get -u github.com/aanupam23/go-stellar-ipfs  Getting Started go-stellar-ipfs is a library that acts as a bridge between Stellar and IPFS. It combines the low fee and fast speed stellar with ipfs. Using this library you can build Stellar and IPFS application very quickly.
go-stellar-ipfs implements StellarShell that helps you use premade functions for sending any sort of data to IPFS using stellar transaction, memo, manage data and also allows reading of that data.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>